
import video4 from "../../assets/video4.mp4"
import video5 from "../../assets/video5.mp4"
import video6 from "../../assets/video6.mp4"
import video7 from "../../assets/video7.mp4"
import video8 from "../../assets/video8.mp4"
import video9 from "../../assets/video9.mp4"
import video10 from "../../assets/video10.mp4"
import video11 from "../../assets/video11.mp4"
import video12 from "../../assets/video12.mp4"
import video13 from "../../assets/video13.mp4"
import video15 from "../../assets/video15.mp4"
import video16 from "../../assets/video16.mp4"
import video18 from "../../assets/video18.mp4"
import video21 from "../../assets/video21.mp4"
import video24 from "../../assets/video24.mp4"
import video26 from "../../assets/video26.mp4"
import video27 from "../../assets/video27.mp4"
import video28 from "../../assets/video28.mp4"
import video29 from "../../assets/video29.mp4"
import video31 from "../../assets/video31.mp4"
import video34 from "../../assets/video34.mp4"
import video35 from "../../assets/video35.mp4"
import video37 from "../../assets/video37.mp4"
import video38 from "../../assets/video38.mp4"
import video39 from "../../assets/video39.mp4"
import video40 from "../../assets/video40.mp4"
import video41 from "../../assets/video41.mp4"
import video42 from "../../assets/video42.mp4"
import video43 from "../../assets/video43.mp4"
import video44 from "../../assets/video44.mp4"
import video45 from "../../assets/video45.mp4"
import video46 from "../../assets/video46.mp4"
import video47 from "../../assets/video47.mp4"
import video49 from "../../assets/video49.mp4"
import video50 from "../../assets/video50.mp4"
import video51 from "../../assets/video51.mp4"
import video52 from "../../assets/video52.mp4"
import video53 from "../../assets/video53.mp4"
import video54 from "../../assets/video54.mp4"
import video56 from "../../assets/video56.mp4"
import video57 from "../../assets/video57.mp4"
import video58 from "../../assets/video58.mp4"
import video60 from "../../assets/video60.mp4"
import video61 from "../../assets/video61.mp4"
import video62 from "../../assets/video62.mp4"
import video63 from "../../assets/video63.mp4"
import video64 from "../../assets/video64.mp4"
import video65 from "../../assets/video65.mp4"
import video67 from "../../assets/video67.mp4"
import video69 from "../../assets/video69.mp4"
import video71 from "../../assets/video71.mp4"
import video72 from "../../assets/video72.mp4"
import video73 from "../../assets/video73.mp4"
import video77 from "../../assets/video77.mp4"
import video78 from "../../assets/video78.mp4"
import video79 from "../../assets/video79.mp4"
import video80 from "../../assets/video80.mp4"
import video82 from "../../assets/video82.mp4"
import video83 from "../../assets/video83.mp4"
import video84 from "../../assets/video84.mp4"
import video85 from "../../assets/video85.mp4"
import video86 from "../../assets/video86.mp4"
import video90 from "../../assets/video90.mp4"
import video92 from "../../assets/video92.mp4"
import video93 from "../../assets/video93.mp4"
import video96 from "../../assets/video96.mp4"
import video97 from "../../assets/video97.mp4"
import video98 from "../../assets/video98.mp4"
import video103 from "../../assets/video103.mp4"
import video104 from "../../assets/video104.mp4"
import video105 from "../../assets/video105.mp4"
import video108 from "../../assets/video108.mp4"
import video109 from "../../assets/video109.mp4"
import video110 from "../../assets/video110.mp4"
import video111 from "../../assets/video111.mp4"
import video118 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video118.mp4"
import video121 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video121.mp4"
import video122 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video122.mp4"
import video123 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video123.mp4"
import video125 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video125.mp4"
import video126 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video126.mp4"
import video128 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video128.mp4"
import video129 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video129.mp4"
import video132 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video132.mp4"
import video134 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video134.mp4"
import video135 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video135.mp4"
import video136 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video136.mp4"
import video137 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video137.mp4"
import video139 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video139.mp4"
import video140 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video140.mp4"
import video141 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video141.mp4"
import video143 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video143.mp4"
import video144 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video144.mp4"
import video145 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video145.mp4"
import video146 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video146.mp4"
import video147 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video147.mp4"
import video148 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video148.mp4"
import video150 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video150.mp4"
import video152 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video152.mp4"
import video153 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video153.mp4"
import video154 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video154.mp4"
import video155 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video155.mp4"
import video156 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video156.mp4"
import video157 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video157.mp4"
import video158 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video158.mp4"
import video160 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video160.mp4"
import video161 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video161.mp4"
import video162 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video162.mp4"
import video163 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video163.mp4"
import video164 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video164.mp4"
import video165 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video165.mp4"
import video166 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video166.mp4"
import video167 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video167.mp4"
import video171 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video171.mp4"
import video172 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video172.mp4"
import video173 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video173.mp4"
import video174 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video174.mp4"
import video176 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video176.mp4"
import video177 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video177.mp4"
import video179 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video179.mp4"
import video180 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video180.mp4"
import video181 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video181.mp4"
import video183 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video183.mp4"
import video185 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video185.mp4"
import video186 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video186.mp4"
import video188 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video188.mp4"
import video189 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video189.mp4"
import video190 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video190.mp4"
import video191 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video191.mp4"
import video192 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video192.mp4"
import video193 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video193.mp4"
import video194 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video194.mp4"
import video195 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video195.mp4"
import video196 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video196.mp4"
import video197 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video197.mp4"
import video199 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video199.mp4"
import video200 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video200.mp4"
import video201 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video201.mp4"
import video202 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video202.mp4"
import video204 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video204.mp4"
import video205 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video205.mp4"
import video206 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video206.mp4"
import video207 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video207.mp4"
import video208 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video208.mp4"
import video209 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video209.mp4"
import video210 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video210.mp4"
import video211 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video211.mp4"
import video212 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video212.mp4"
import video213 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video213.mp4"
import video214 from "../../assets2_hotelTransilvania/video214.mp4"
import video215 from "../../assets3_pets/video215.mp4"
import video216 from "../../assets3_pets/video216.mp4"
import video217 from "../../assets3_pets/video217.mp4"
import video218 from "../../assets3_pets/video218.mp4"
import video219 from "../../assets3_pets/video219.mp4"
import video220 from "../../assets3_pets/video220.mp4"
import video221 from "../../assets3_pets/video221.mp4"
import video222 from "../../assets3_pets/video222.mp4"
import video223 from "../../assets3_pets/video223.mp4"
import video224 from "../../assets3_pets/video224.mp4"
import video225 from "../../assets3_pets/video225.mp4"
import video226 from "../../assets3_pets/video226.mp4"
import video227 from "../../assets3_pets/video227.mp4"
import video228 from "../../assets3_pets/video228.mp4"
import video229 from "../../assets3_pets/video229.mp4"
import video230 from "../../assets3_pets/video230.mp4"
import video231 from "../../assets3_pets/video231.mp4"
import video232 from "../../assets3_pets/video232.mp4"
import video233 from "../../assets3_pets/video233.mp4"
import video234 from "../../assets3_pets/video234.mp4"
import video235 from "../../assets3_pets/video235.mp4"
import video236 from "../../assets3_pets/video236.mp4"
import video237 from "../../assets3_pets/video237.mp4"
import video238 from "../../assets3_pets/video238.mp4"
import video239 from "../../assets3_pets/video239.mp4"
import video240 from "../../assets3_pets/video240.mp4"
import video241 from "../../assets3_pets/video241.mp4"
import video242 from "../../assets3_pets/video242.mp4"
import video243 from "../../assets3_pets/video243.mp4"
import video244 from "../../assets3_pets/video244.mp4"
import video245 from "../../assets3_pets/video245.mp4"
import video246 from "../../assets3_pets/video246.mp4"
import video247 from "../../assets3_pets/video247.mp4"
import video248 from "../../assets3_pets/video248.mp4"
import video249 from "../../assets3_pets/video249.mp4"
import video250 from "../../assets3_pets/video250.mp4"
import video251 from "../../assets3_pets/video251.mp4"
import video252 from "../../assets3_pets/video252.mp4"
import video253 from "../../assets3_pets/video253.mp4"
import video254 from "../../assets3_pets/video254.mp4"
import video255 from "../../assets3_pets/video255.mp4"
import video256 from "../../assets3_pets/video256.mp4"
import video257 from "../../assets3_pets/video257.mp4"
import video258 from "../../assets3_pets/video258.mp4"
import video259 from "../../assets3_pets/video259.mp4"
import video260 from "../../assets3_pets/video260.mp4"
import video261 from "../../assets3_pets/video261.mp4"
import video262 from "../../assets3_pets/video262.mp4"
import video263 from "../../assets3_pets/video263.mp4"
import video264 from "../../assets3_pets/video264.mp4"
import video265 from "../../assets3_pets/video265.mp4"
import video266 from "../../assets3_pets/video266.mp4"
import video267 from "../../assets3_pets/video267.mp4"
import video268 from "../../assets3_pets/video268.mp4"
import video269 from "../../assets3_pets/video269.mp4"
import video270 from "../../assets3_pets/video270.mp4"
import video271 from "../../assets3_pets/video271.mp4"
import video272 from "../../assets3_pets/video272.mp4"
import video273 from "../../assets3_pets/video273.mp4"
import video274 from "../../assets3_pets/video274.mp4"
import video275 from "../../assets3_pets/video275.mp4"
import video276 from "../../assets3_pets/video276.mp4"
import video277 from "../../assets3_pets/video277.mp4"
import video278 from "../../4vegas/vegas278.mp4"
import video279 from "../../4vegas/vegas279.mp4"
import video280 from "../../4vegas/vegas280.mp4"
import video281 from "../../4vegas/vegas281.mp4"
import video282 from "../../4vegas/vegas282.mp4"
import video283 from "../../4vegas/vegas283.mp4"
import video284 from "../../4vegas/vegas284.mp4"
import video285 from "../../4vegas/vegas285.mp4"
import video286 from "../../4vegas/vegas286.mp4"
import video287 from "../../4vegas/vegas287.mp4"
import video288 from "../../4vegas/vegas288.mp4"
import video289 from "../../4vegas/vegas289.mp4"
import video290 from "../../4vegas/vegas290.mp4"
import video291 from "../../4vegas/vegas291.mp4"
import video292 from "../../4vegas/vegas292.mp4"
import video293 from "../../4vegas/vegas293.mp4"
import video294 from "../../4vegas/vegas294.mp4"
import video295 from "../../4vegas/vegas295.mp4"
import video296 from "../../4vegas/vegas296.mp4"
import video297 from "../../4vegas/vegas297.mp4"
import video298 from "../../4vegas/vegas298.mp4"
import video299 from "../../4vegas/vegas299.mp4"
import video300 from "../../4vegas/vegas300.mp4"
import video301 from "../../4vegas/vegas301.mp4"
import video302 from "../../4vegas/vegas302.mp4"
import video303 from "../../4vegas/vegas303.mp4"
import video304 from "../../4vegas/vegas304.mp4"
import video305 from "../../4vegas/vegas305.mp4"
import video306 from "../../4vegas/vegas306.mp4"
import video307 from "../../4vegas/vegas307.mp4"
import video308 from "../../4vegas/vegas308.mp4"
import video309 from "../../4vegas/vegas309.mp4"
import video310 from "../../4vegas/vegas310.mp4"
import video311 from "../../4vegas/vegas311.mp4"
import video312 from "../../4vegas/vegas312.mp4"
import video313 from "../../4vegas/vegas313.mp4"
import video314 from "../../4vegas/vegas314.mp4"
import video315 from "../../4vegas/vegas315.mp4"
import video316 from "../../4vegas/vegas316.mp4"
import video317 from "../../4vegas/vegas317.mp4"
import video318 from "../../4vegas/vegas318.mp4"
import video319 from "../../4vegas/vegas319.mp4"
import video320 from "../../4vegas/vegas320.mp4"
import video321 from "../../4vegas/vegas321.mp4"
import video322 from "../../4vegas/vegas322.mp4"
import video323 from "../../4vegas/vegas323.mp4"
import video324 from "../../4vegas/vegas324.mp4"
import video325 from "../../4vegas/vegas325.mp4"
import video326 from "../../4vegas/vegas326.mp4"
import video327 from "../../4vegas/vegas327.mp4"
import video328 from "../../4vegas/vegas328.mp4"
import video329 from "../../4vegas/vegas329.mp4"
import video330 from "../../4vegas/vegas330.mp4"
import video331 from "../../4vegas/vegas331.mp4"
import video332 from "../../4vegas/vegas332.mp4"
import video333 from "../../4vegas/vegas333.mp4"
import video334 from "../../4vegas/vegas334.mp4"
import video335 from "../../4vegas/vegas335.mp4"
import video336 from "../../4vegas/vegas336.mp4"
import video337 from "../../4vegas/vegas337.mp4"
import video338 from "../../4vegas/vegas338.mp4"
import video339 from "../../4vegas/vegas339.mp4"
import video340 from "../../4vegas/vegas340.mp4"
import video341 from "../../4vegas/vegas341.mp4"
import video342 from "../../4vegas/vegas342.mp4"
import video343 from "../../4vegas/vegas343.mp4"
import video344 from "../../4vegas/vegas344.mp4"
import video345 from "../../4vegas/vegas345.mp4"
import video346 from "../../4vegas/vegas346.mp4"
import video347 from "../../4vegas/vegas347.mp4"
import video348 from "../../4vegas/vegas348.mp4"
import video349 from "../../4vegas/vegas349.mp4"
import video350 from "../../4vegas/vegas350.mp4"
import video351 from "../../4vegas/vegas351.mp4"
import video352 from "../../4vegas/vegas352.mp4"
import video353 from "../../4vegas/vegas353.mp4"
import video354 from "../../4vegas/vegas354.mp4"
import video355 from "../../4vegas/vegas355.mp4"


 export const new_data = [
    {
        id: 270,
        videoFile: video312,
        rusQuestion: "мякоть",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a soft, wet mass, often produced by crushing something:",
        answer: "pulp",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 269,
        videoFile: video311,
        rusQuestion: "сумочка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a handbag or a small container for money, usually used by a woman:",
        answer: "purse",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 268,
        videoFile: video311,
        rusQuestion: "меня вырвало",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to vomit:",
        answer: "I threw up",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 267,
        videoFile: video310,
        rusQuestion: "вмешательство",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the action of becoming intentionally involved in a difficult situation, in order to improve it or prevent it from getting worse:",
        answer: "intervention",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 266,
        videoFile: video309,
        rusQuestion: "рикошет",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to bounce back after hitting a hard surface",
        answer: "rebound",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 265,
        videoFile: video308,
        rusQuestion: "аннулирование",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an official announcement that something such as a law, agreement, or marriage no longer exists, or the process of making this announcement:",
        answer: "annulment",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 264,
        videoFile: video307,
        rusQuestion: "буфет",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a meal where people serve themselves different types of food:",
        answer: "buffet",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 263,
        videoFile: video306,
        rusQuestion: "пошел ты",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "It means 'fuck you' but is far more polite.",
        answer: "screw you",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 262,
        videoFile: video305,
        rusQuestion: "приветствую это",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a friendly expression said just before you drink an alcoholic drink:",
        answer: "cheers to that",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 261,
        videoFile: video304,
        rusQuestion: "в моей области",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "в моей области, в которой я работаю",
        answer: "in my field",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 260,
        videoFile: video303,
        rusQuestion: "попробуй",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to ask someone to do something that involves risk:",
        answer: "I dare you",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 259,
        videoFile: video302,
        rusQuestion: "наметить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to plan something in detail:",
        answer: "to map out",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 258,
        videoFile: video301,
        rusQuestion: "шалава",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an unpleasant person, especially a woman who has sex with a lot of different people",
        answer: "skank",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 257,
        videoFile: video300,
        rusQuestion: "удобства , удовольствия",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "something, such as a swimming pool or shopping centre, that is intended to make life more pleasant or comfortable for the people in a town, hotel, or other place:",
        answer: "amenities",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 256,
        videoFile: video299,
        rusQuestion: "люкс",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a set of connected rooms, especially in a hotel:",
        answer: "suite",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 255,
        videoFile: video298,
        rusQuestion: "враждебный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "unfriendly and not liking something:",
        answer: "hostile",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 254,
        videoFile: video297,
        rusQuestion: "в конце концов",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "in the end, especially after a long time or a lot of effort, problems, etc.:",
        answer: "eventually",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 253,
        videoFile: video296,
        rusQuestion: "обновление , подъем",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to improve the quality or usefulness of something, or change it for something newer or of a better standard:",
        answer: "upgrade",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 252,
        videoFile: video295,
        rusQuestion: "жених",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the man who someone is engaged to be married to:",
        answer: "fiance",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 251,
        videoFile: video294,
        rusQuestion: "потерпите нас",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to be patient with someone or something:",
        answer: "bear with us",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 250,
        videoFile: video293,
        rusQuestion: "беззаботный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "having no problems or not being worried about anything:",
        answer: "carefree",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 249,
        videoFile: video292,
        rusQuestion: "извлечь из этого выгоду , превращать в капитал",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to use a situation to your own advantage:",
        answer: "capitalize on",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 248,
        videoFile: video291,
        rusQuestion: "по дороге",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "while they were coming to that spot",
        answer: "on the way over",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 247,
        videoFile: video290,
        rusQuestion: "корчится",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to make twisting movements with the body, esp. because you are feeling strong emotion:",
        answer: "writhing",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 246,
        videoFile: video289,
        rusQuestion: "он перевернется",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to fall over suddenly: If a boat oooooo, it turns upside down in the water:",
        answer: "keel over",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 245,
        videoFile: video288,
        rusQuestion: "в последнее время",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "Lately; recently.",
        answer: "as of late",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 244,
        videoFile: video287,
        rusQuestion: "бескорыстный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "caring more for what other people need and want rather than for what you yourself need and want:",
        answer: "selfless",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 243,
        videoFile: video286,
        rusQuestion: "переборщить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to do something too much, or to be too excited or eager about something:",
        answer: "go overboard",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 242,
        videoFile: video285,
        rusQuestion: "перерезать шнур , веревка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to end a connection with someone Source: theidioms.com , to do something that makes one independent Source: theidioms.com",
        answer: "cut the cord",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 241,
        videoFile: video284,
        rusQuestion: "талоны на питание",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a piece of paper that is given to poor people by the government and with which they can then buy food",
        answer: "food stamp",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 240,
        videoFile: video283,
        rusQuestion: "душа компании",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "someone who is energetic and funny and at the centre of activity during social occasions",
        answer: "life of the party",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 239,
        videoFile: video282,
        rusQuestion: "без рубашки",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the one who is not wearing a shirt",
        answer: "shirtless",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 238,
        videoFile: video281,
        rusQuestion: "распутная",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "looking like or relating to a person, especially a woman, who has a lot of sexual relationships without any emotional involvement:",
        answer: "slutty",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 237,
        videoFile: video280,
        rusQuestion: "установка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the time and the place in which the action of a book, film, play, etc. happens:",
        answer: "setting",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 236,
        videoFile: video279,
        rusQuestion: "темп",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the speed at which someone or something moves, or with which something happens or changes:",
        answer: "pace",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 235,
        videoFile: video278,
        rusQuestion: "росток",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to produce leaves, hair, or other new developing parts, or (of leaves, hair, and other developing parts) to begin to grow:",
        answer: "sprout",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 234,
        videoFile: video277,
        rusQuestion: "падение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(something that causes) the usually sudden destruction of a person, organization, or government and their loss of power, money, or health:",
        answer: "downfall",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 233,
        videoFile: video276,
        rusQuestion: "подвезти кого-нибудь",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to make someone happier:",
        answer: "give a lift",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 232,
        videoFile: video275,
        rusQuestion: "держит под контролем",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to limit something:",
        answer: "keeping in check",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 231,
        videoFile: video274,
        rusQuestion: "дыра в дорожном покрытии",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a hole in a road surface that results from gradual damage caused by traffic and/or weather:",
        answer: "pothole",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 230,
        videoFile: video273,
        rusQuestion: "повестись на это",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to be tricked into believing something that is not true:",
        answer: "fall for it",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 229,
        videoFile: video272,
        rusQuestion: "ты тормозишь?",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to stop making progress:  to delay taking action or avoid giving an answer in order to have more time to make a decision or get an advantage:",
        answer: "stall",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 228,
        videoFile: video271,
        rusQuestion: "лампочка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a glass or transparent container, usually rounded, with something inside that produces light when an electric current passes through it, such as an electric filament (= a thin thread of metal) or an LED (= an electronic device):",
        answer: "light bulb",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 227,
        videoFile: video270,
        rusQuestion: "новаторский",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "original and important; showing a new way of doing or thinking about things:",
        answer: "groundbreaking",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 226,
        videoFile: video269,
        rusQuestion: "с облегчением",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "happy that something unpleasant has not happened or has ended:",
        answer: "relieved",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 225,
        videoFile: video268,
        rusQuestion: "настигнуть , догнать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to reach someone in front of you by going faster than them:",
        answer: "catch up with",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 224,
        videoFile: video267,
        rusQuestion: "Гайка отвинтилась",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "If you say that someone has a oooo, you mean that they behave in a strange way and seem slightly mentally ill.",
        answer: "got a screw loose",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 223,
        videoFile: video266,
        rusQuestion: "отомщенный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to do harm to or punish the person responsible for something bad done to you or your family or friends in order to achieve a fair situation:",
        answer: "avenged",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 222,
        videoFile: video265,
        rusQuestion: "вспыльчивые",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "easily annoyed and not patient:  lacking patience and feeling upset:",
        answer: "testy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 221,
        videoFile: video264,
        rusQuestion: "медленные люди",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "someone, especially a child, who is walking or doing something too slowly",
        answer: "slowpoke",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 220,
        videoFile: video263,
        rusQuestion: "никогда не знаешь",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a story or situation, often dangerous or of great importance, where two opposite results are possible and you do not know what the result will be until the last moment:",
        answer: "cliffhanger",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 219,
        videoFile: video262,
        rusQuestion: "щенок",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a young dog:",
        answer: "puppy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 218,
        videoFile: video261,
        rusQuestion: "первобытный инстинкт",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "basic and relating to an early stage of development:  the way people or animals naturally react or behave, without having to think or learn about it:",
        answer: "primal instinct",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 217,
        videoFile: video260,
        rusQuestion: "произошел от",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to have developed from something that existed in the past:",
        answer: "descended from",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 216,
        videoFile: video259,
        rusQuestion: "пушистый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "not clear: A oooo surface feels like short fur:",
        answer: "fuzzy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 215,
        videoFile: video258,
        rusQuestion: "размытие , неясные очертания",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "something that you cannot see clearly:",
        answer: "blur",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 214,
        videoFile: video257,
        rusQuestion: "как будто готово",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "almost:",
        answer: "as good as",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 213,
        videoFile: video256,
        rusQuestion: "соединение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a place where people go for entertainment, especially one that has a bad reputation:",
        answer: "joint",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 212,
        videoFile: video255,
        rusQuestion: "двигаться с пыхтением",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to make the sound of an engine or motor, or to move making this sound:",
        answer: "chug",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 211,
        videoFile: video254,
        rusQuestion: "собачье весло",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a simple swimming action in which a person moves their arms and legs up and down in quick movements under the water",
        answer: "doggy paddle",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 210,
        videoFile: video253,
        rusQuestion: "ястреб",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a type of large bird that catches small birds and animals for food",
        answer: "hawk",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 209,
        videoFile: video252,
        rusQuestion: "хитрый , изворотливый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "looking or seeming dishonest:",
        answer: "shifty",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 208,
        videoFile: video251,
        rusQuestion: "захватить власть",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to start doing a job or being responsible for something that another person did or had responsibility for before:",
        answer: "take over",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 207,
        videoFile: video250,
        rusQuestion: "запоздалый , просроченный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "not done or happening when expected or when needed; late:",
        answer: "overdue",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 206,
        videoFile: video249,
        rusQuestion: "лепешка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a pancake (= a sweet, thick cake eaten hot, usually for breakfast)",
        answer: "flapjack",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 205,
        videoFile: video248,
        rusQuestion: "сплющенный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: " to crush something that is soft: to crush something, or to make the sound you make when you walk through something soft and wet:",
        answer: "squished",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 204,
        videoFile: video247,
        rusQuestion: "отрезанный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "ooooer a person who kills or injures people using a knife",
        answer: "slashed off",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 203,
        videoFile: video247,
        rusQuestion: "переулок",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a narrow road or path between buildings:",
        answer: "alley",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 202,
        videoFile: video246,
        rusQuestion: "преданность",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "loyalty and support for a ruler, country, group, or belief:",
        answer: "allegiance",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 200,
        videoFile: video244,
        rusQuestion: "салон",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a business that provides a stated type of personal service or sells a stated product:",
        answer: "parlor",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 199,
        videoFile: video243,
        rusQuestion: "прилавок",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a long, flat, narrow surface or table in a shop, bank, restaurant, etc. at which people are served:",
        answer: "counter",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 198,
        videoFile: video242,
        rusQuestion: "кровавые подробности",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the interesting and usually personal pieces of information about a person or event:",
        answer: "gory details",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 197,
        videoFile: video241,
        rusQuestion: "низ живота",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a hidden unpleasant or criminal part of society. the weakest or most unpleasant part of something:",
        answer: "underbelly",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 196,
        videoFile: video240,
        rusQuestion: "мошеннически",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "in a way that suggests someone is doing something that is slightly bad or wrong, but that is not too serious:",
        answer: "roguishly",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 195,
        videoFile: video239,
        rusQuestion: "предвестник беды",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a feeling that something very bad is going to happen soon:",
        answer: "foreboding",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 194,
        videoFile: video238,
        rusQuestion: "Покойся с миром",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "rest in peace  . is often written on a gravestone as a wish that the person buried there will have peace in death.",
        answer: "r.i.p.",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 193,
        videoFile: video237,
        rusQuestion: "ошейник , воротник",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a strap made of leather or other strong material that is put around the neck of an animal, especially a dog or cat: the part around the neck of a piece of clothing, usually sewn on and sometimes made of different material:",
        answer: "collar",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 192,
        videoFile: video236,
        rusQuestion: "вырваться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(informal) 1to escape from a place such as a prison",
        answer: "busting out",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 191,
        videoFile: video235,
        rusQuestion: "тюрьма , загон",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a place where pets that are lost or not wanted are kept:",
        answer: "pound",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 190,
        videoFile: video234,
        rusQuestion: "удирать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to go away quickly:",
        answer: "scram",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 189,
        videoFile: video233,
        rusQuestion: "изюм",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a dried black grape",
        answer: "raisin",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 188,
        videoFile: video232,
        rusQuestion: "парень",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a boy or young man:",
        answer: "lad",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 187,
        videoFile: video231,
        rusQuestion: "поводок",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a piece of rope, chain, etc. tied to an animal, especially to a dog at its collar when taking it for a walk:",
        answer: "leash",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 186,
        videoFile: video230,
        rusQuestion: "бродить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to travel along a route that was not originally intended, or to move outside a limited area:",
        answer: "stray",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 185,
        videoFile: video229,
        rusQuestion: "разгромлен",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to cause a lot of damage to something:",
        answer: "trashed",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 184,
        videoFile: video228,
        rusQuestion: "вывернуться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to become extremely angry or to lose control of yourself from surprise or shock:",
        answer: "flip out",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 183,
        videoFile: video227,
        rusQuestion: "тупой",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "stupid : unable to speak:",
        answer: "dumb",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 182,
        videoFile: video226,
        rusQuestion: "подвинуться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to slide while sitting:  to go quickly:",
        answer: "scoot on",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 181,
        videoFile: video225,
        rusQuestion: "одеяло",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a flat cover made of wool or similar warm material, usually used on a bed",
        answer: "blanket",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 180,
        videoFile: video224,
        rusQuestion: "понять и принять",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to understand completely the meaning or importance of something:",
        answer: "take in",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 179,
        videoFile: video223,
        rusQuestion: "взволнованный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "excited:",
        answer: "psyched",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 178,
        videoFile: video222,
        rusQuestion: "гарантированный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "used to say that something is sure to happen or be true:",
        answer: "guaranteed",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 177,
        videoFile: video221,
        rusQuestion: "потерять сознание",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to become unconscious for a short time, for example when ill, badly hurt, or drunk:",
        answer: "pass out",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 176,
        videoFile: video220,
        rusQuestion: "чемодан",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a large, rectangular container with a handle, for carrying clothes and possessions while travelling:",
        answer: "suitcase",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 175,
        videoFile: video219,
        rusQuestion: "почти",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "almost completely:",
        answer: "pretty much",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 174,
        videoFile: video218,
        rusQuestion: "родственные души",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "someone, usually your romantic or sexual partner, who you have a special relationship with, and who you know and love very much:",
        answer: "soulmate",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 173,
        videoFile: video217,
        rusQuestion: "с тех пор",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "continuously since that time:",
        answer: "ever since",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 172,
        videoFile: video216,
        rusQuestion: "въезжать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to go to a different place and begin to live or work there:",
        answer: "move in",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    }, 
    {
        id: 171,
        videoFile: video215,
        rusQuestion: "светится",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "shining with light and colour:",
        answer: "aglow",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 170,
        videoFile: video205,
        rusQuestion: "зашитый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a piece of thread sewn in cloth, or the single movement of a needle and thread into and out of the cloth that produces this:",
        answer: "stitched shut",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 169,
        videoFile: video199,
        rusQuestion: "выскальзывать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to go somewhere quietly because you do not want anyone to hear you",
        answer: "sneak out",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 168,
        videoFile: video214,
        rusQuestion: "предосторожность",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an action that is done to prevent something unpleasant or dangerous happening:",
        answer: "precaution",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 167,
        videoFile: video213,
        rusQuestion: "тушеное мясо",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a type of food consisting usually of meat or fish and vegetables cooked slowly in a small amount of liquid:",
        answer: "stew",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 166,
        videoFile: video212,
        rusQuestion: "загар",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "brown skin caused by being in the sun:",
        answer: "tan",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 165,
        videoFile: video211,
        rusQuestion: "точно",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "exactly right:",
        answer: "spot on",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 164,
        videoFile: video210,
        rusQuestion: "бежать по холмам",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to be extremely unwilling to be involved in something, and to avoid it:",
        answer: "run for the hills",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 163,
        videoFile: video209,
        rusQuestion: "странный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "relating to the effect produced by taking a psychedelic drug (= one that affects the mind and the way that someone sees things):",
        answer: "trippy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 162,
        videoFile: video208,
        rusQuestion: "бараньи отбивные",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the area of the face surrounding the mouth of a person or an animal: a small piece of lamb including a rib.",
        answer: "chops",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 161,
        videoFile: video208,
        rusQuestion: "ягненок",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a young sheep, or the flesh of a young sheep eaten as meat:",
        answer: "lamb",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 160,
        videoFile: video207,
        rusQuestion: "подгузник",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a square of thick soft paper or cloth that is fastened around a baby's bottom and between its legs to absorb its urine and solid waste:",
        answer: "diaper",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 159,
        videoFile: video206,
        rusQuestion: "подходящий",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "having the necessary qualities or satisfying the necessary conditions:",
        answer: "eligible",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 158,
        videoFile: video204,
        rusQuestion: "ковыряется в носу",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "To insert a finger or other object into one's nostril to remove obstructions, especially dried mucus.",
        answer: "picking his nose",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 157,
        videoFile: video202,
        rusQuestion: "превзошел",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to be, or do something, better than someone else:",
        answer: "outdid",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 156,
        videoFile: video201,
        rusQuestion: "соска",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: " ,,,pacifier,,, a brand name for a smooth plastic or rubber object that is given to a baby to suck, to stop them from crying or being upset, or to help them sleep:",
        answer: "binky",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id:155,
        videoFile: video200,
        rusQuestion: "вздремнуть",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to sleep for a short time, especially during the day",
        answer: "snooze",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 154,
        videoFile: video197,
        rusQuestion: "противный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "strange and frightening",
        answer: "creepy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 153,
        videoFile: video196,
        rusQuestion: "это грубо",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "extremely unpleasant: rude or offensive:  extreme in a way that is very obviously wrong and unacceptable:",
        answer: "gross",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 152,
        videoFile: video195,
        rusQuestion: "зад",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the back end of an animal  , a person's bottom",
        answer: "rump",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 151,
        videoFile: video194,
        rusQuestion: "горб",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a round raised part on a person's or animal's back:",
        answer: "hump",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 150,
        videoFile: video194,
        rusQuestion: "натыкаетесь",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to hurt part of your body by hitting it against something hard: to hit something with force:",
        answer: "bump",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 149,
        videoFile: video193,
        rusQuestion: "неуклюжий",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "difficult to use, do, or deal with: causing problems, worry, or embarrassment:",
        answer: "awkward",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 148,
        videoFile: video192,
        rusQuestion: "спорный вопрос",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "An issue that is subject to, or open for, discussion or debate, to which no satisfactory answer is found",
        answer: "moot point",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 147,
        videoFile: video191,
        rusQuestion: "поладить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to be friendly with each other immediately:",
        answer: "hit it off",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 146,
        videoFile: video190,
        rusQuestion: "засунуть",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to push someone or something forcefully:",
        answer: "shove",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 145,
        videoFile: video189,
        rusQuestion: "сдутый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "If something that has air or gas inside it ooooes, or is deflated, it becomes smaller because it loses the air or gas:",
        answer: "deflated",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 144,
        videoFile: video188,
        rusQuestion: "отвратительный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "extremely unpleasant or unacceptable:",
        answer: "disgusting",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 143,
        videoFile: video186,
        rusQuestion: "воспитанный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "past simple and past participle of breed , to keep animals for the purpose of producing young animals in a controlled way:",
        answer: "bred",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 142,
        videoFile: video185,
        rusQuestion: "грубое обращение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to fight in a way that is not serious: to play in a rough and noisy way:",
        answer: "roughhouse",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 141,
        videoFile: video183,
        rusQuestion: "бублик",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a type of bread that is small, hard, and in the shape of a ring:",
        answer: "bagel",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 140,
        videoFile: video181,
        rusQuestion: "поворот , изгибаться , крутить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to turn something, especially repeatedly, or to turn or wrap one thing around another:",
        answer: "twist",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 139,
        videoFile: video180,
        rusQuestion: "боком , в сторону",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "in a direction to the left or right, not forwards or backwards:",
        answer: "sideways",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 138,
        videoFile: video179,
        rusQuestion: "это не было подсказкой",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to give someone a sign or some information that helps them to find the answer to a problem, question, or mystery:",
        answer: "give a clue",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 137,
        videoFile: video177,
        rusQuestion: "быстро съесть (что-то)",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to eat (something) quickly",
        answer: "scarfing down",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 136,
        videoFile: video176,
        rusQuestion: "ровесник",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a person who is of the same age as you:  existing or happening now, and therefore seeming modern:",
        answer: "contemporary",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 135,
        videoFile: video174,
        rusQuestion: "аккуратный , изящный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "tidy, with everything in its place:  clever and simple:",
        answer: "neat",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 134,
        videoFile: video173,
        rusQuestion: "кол",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "in the past, a wooden post to which people were tied before being burned to death as a punishment:",
        answer: "stake",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 133,
        videoFile: video172,
        rusQuestion: "набухает",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to become larger and rounder than usual; to (cause to) increase in size or amount:",
        answer: "swell",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 132,
        videoFile: video171,
        rusQuestion: "тусоваться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to spend a lot of time in a place or with someone:",
        answer: "hang out",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 131,
        videoFile: video167,
        rusQuestion: "подвести итог",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a short, clear description that gives the main facts or ideas about something:",
        answer: "sum up",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 130,
        videoFile: video166,
        rusQuestion: "спокойствие",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a peaceful, calm state, without noise, violence, worry, etc.:",
        answer: "tranquility",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 129,
        videoFile: video165,
        rusQuestion: "лишенный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "without; lacking in:",
        answer: "void of",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 128,
        videoFile: video164,
        rusQuestion: "преследование , гонение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "unfair or cruel treatment over a long period of time because of race, religion, or political beliefs:",
        answer: "persecution",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 127,
        videoFile: video163,
        rusQuestion: "скрывающийся",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a ooooo person or animal is waiting where he, she, or it cannot be seen, usually waiting to attack or do something bad:",
        answer: "lurking",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 126,
        videoFile: video162,
        rusQuestion: "заменитель",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to use something or someone instead of another thing or person:",
        answer: "substitute",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 125,
        videoFile: video161,
        rusQuestion: "жирный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "containing a lot of fat:",
        answer: "fatty",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 124,
        videoFile: video160,
        rusQuestion: "все сходят с ума",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to be very excited or emotional, or to cause someone be this way:",
        answer: "freak out",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 123,
        videoFile: video158,
        rusQuestion: "рюкзак",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a large bag used to carry things on your back, used especially by people who go camping or walking:",
        answer: "backpack",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 122,
        videoFile: video157,
        rusQuestion: "болтовня",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to talk or say something in a quick, confused, excited, or silly way:",
        answer: "babble",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 121,
        videoFile: video156,
        rusQuestion: "убежище , святилище",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "protection or a safe place, especially for someone or something being chased or hunted:",
        answer: "sanctuary",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 120,
        videoFile: video155,
        rusQuestion: "пух",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "small, loose pieces of wool or other soft material, or the down (= soft new hairs) on a young animal:",
        answer: "fluff",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 119,
        videoFile: video154,
        rusQuestion: "совок",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a flat container with a handle into which you brush dust and dirt",
        answer: "dustpan",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 118,
        videoFile: video153,
        rusQuestion: "вонючий",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "having a bad smell or appearance:",
        answer: "funky",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 117,
        videoFile: video152,
        rusQuestion: "молодежное общежитие",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a place where people, especially young people, can stay cheaply for short periods when they are travelling",
        answer: "youth hostel",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 116,
        videoFile: video150,
        rusQuestion: "вынюхивать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to go somewhere secretly, or to take someone or something somewhere secretly:",
        answer: "sneaking around",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 115,
        videoFile: video148,
        rusQuestion: "Берегись",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to be careful to notice someone or something interesting:",
        answer: "watch out for",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 114,
        videoFile: video147,
        rusQuestion: "вычерпывать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to remove something that is inside something else with a spoon:",
        answer: "scoop out",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 113,
        videoFile: video146,
        rusQuestion: "беспощадный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "oooo people or actions show an intention or wish to hurt someone or something very badly:",
        answer: "vicious",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 112,
        videoFile: video145,
        rusQuestion: "надутый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "used to describe lips that are pushed forward, especially because someone is intentionally doing this in order to look more sexually attractive:",
        answer: "pouty",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 111,
        videoFile: video144,
        rusQuestion: "бешенство",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a serious disease of the nervous system that can cause death. ooooo can be passed on to humans by other animals:",
        answer: "rabies",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 110,
        videoFile: video143,
        rusQuestion: "я все понял",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "It's usually like ,I'll take care of it, or ,I'll do it.",
        answer: "I got it covered",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 109,
        videoFile: video141,
        rusQuestion: "Ваше Высокопреосвященство",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the state of being famous, respected, or important:",
        answer: "your Eminence",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },  
    {
        id: 108,
        videoFile: video121,
        rusQuestion: "лес с привидениями",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "building or other place  where a ghost regularly appears.",
        answer: "haunted forest",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 107,
        videoFile: video140,
        rusQuestion: "злодей",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a bad person who harms other people or breaks the law:",
        answer: "villain",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 106,
        videoFile: video139,
        rusQuestion: "задушить нас",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to kill someone by pressing their throat so that they cannot breathe:",
        answer: "to strangle us",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 105,
        videoFile: video137,
        rusQuestion: "обнаружил",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to discover something secret or hidden :",
        answer: "has uncovered",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 104,
        videoFile: video136,
        rusQuestion: "наблюдение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the careful watching of a person or place, especially by the police or army, because of a crime that has happened or is expected:",
        answer: "surveillance",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 103,
        videoFile: video135,
        rusQuestion: "убежище",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(a place that gives) protection or shelter from danger, trouble, unhappiness, etc.:",
        answer: "refuge",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 102,
        videoFile: video134,
        rusQuestion: "вне опасности",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "no longer in difficulty or trouble. out of danger; free from obligation or guilt",
        answer: "off the hook",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 101,
        videoFile: video132,
        rusQuestion: "неотразимый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "impossible to refuse, oppose, or avoid because it is too pleasant, attractive, or strong:",
        answer: "irresistible",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 100,
        videoFile: video129,
        rusQuestion: "грязь",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "thick, unpleasant dirt:",
        answer: "filth",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 99,
        videoFile: video128,
        rusQuestion: "кладбище",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an area of ground in which dead bodies are buried",
        answer: "cemetery",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 98,
        videoFile: video126,
        rusQuestion: "забитый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "blocked or filled with something:",
        answer: "clogged",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 97,
        videoFile: video125,
        rusQuestion: "сантехника",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the water pipes and similar systems in a building:",
        answer: "plumbing",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 96,
        videoFile: video123,
        rusQuestion: "путеводитель",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a detailed plan or route of a journey:",
        answer: "itinerary",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 95,
        videoFile: video122,
        rusQuestion: "костер",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a large fire that is made outside to burn unwanted things, or for pleasure",
        answer: "bonfire",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 94,
        videoFile: video118,
        rusQuestion: "квадратные метры",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the amount of flat space that covers an area",
        answer: "square footage",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    }, 
    {
        id: 93,
        videoFile: video111,
        rusQuestion: "бородавки и все такое",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "describing or including all the bad qualities in a person's character, with no attempt to hide them:",
        answer: "warts and all",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 92,
        videoFile: video110,
        rusQuestion: "квакать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "When animals such as frogs and crows ooooo, they make deep rough sounds.",
        answer: "croak",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 91,
        videoFile: video109,
        rusQuestion: "пена",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a mass of very small bubbles formed on the surface of a liquid",
        answer: "foam",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 90,
        videoFile: video108,
        rusQuestion: "ворочаюсь",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to move about from side to side or turn a lot in bed, especially because you cannot sleep:",
        answer: "toss and turn",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 89,
        videoFile: video105,
        rusQuestion: "выпечка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a food made from a mixture of flour, fat, and water, rolled flat and either wrapped around or put over or under other foods, and then baked:",
        answer: "pastry",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 88,
        videoFile: video104,
        rusQuestion: "ров",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a long, wide hole that is dug all the way around a place such as a castle and usually filled with water, to make it more difficult to attack",
        answer: "moat",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 87,
        videoFile: video103,
        rusQuestion: "перемотать назад",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to make a recording go back towards the beginning:",
        answer: "rewind",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 86,
        videoFile: video98,
        rusQuestion: "отозвать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to decide that a planned event, especially a sports event, will not happen, or to end an activity because it is no longer useful or possible:",
        answer: "to call off",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 85,
        videoFile: video97,
        rusQuestion: "резной",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to make something by cutting into especially wood or stone, or to cut into the surface of stone, wood, etc.:",
        answer: "carved",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 84,
        videoFile: video96,
        rusQuestion: "голубь , простофиля",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a large, usually gray-and-white bird that lives esp. in cities:",
        answer: "pigeon",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 83,
        videoFile: video93,
        rusQuestion: "парик",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a covering of artificial hair worn on the head to hide a loss of hair or to cover your own hair:",
        answer: "wig",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 82,
        videoFile: video92,
        rusQuestion: "сварливый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "arguing and complaining a lot:",
        answer: "cantankerous",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 81,
        videoFile: video90,
        rusQuestion: "ржал",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(of a horse) to make a soft, high sound:",
        answer: "whinny",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 80,
        videoFile: video90,
        rusQuestion: "жеребец",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an adult male horse that is used for breeding",
        answer: "stallion",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 79,
        videoFile: video86,
        rusQuestion: "ударить , прикончить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to give someone or something a hard, noisy hit:  to hit someone or something noisily:",
        answer: "whack",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 78,
        videoFile: video86,
        rusQuestion: "подлый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "dirty, cheap, or not socially acceptable, especially relating to moral or sexual matters:",
        answer: "sleazy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 77,
        videoFile: video85,
        rusQuestion: "недействительный , подделка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "something that has no value or that does not work:",
        answer: "dud",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 76,
        videoFile: video84,
        rusQuestion: "валяться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(especially of some animals) to lie or roll around slowly in deep, wet earth, sand, or water:",
        answer: "wallowing",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 75,
        videoFile: video83,
        rusQuestion: "за нас",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "said when asking a group of people to hold up their glasses and then drink as an expression of good wishes to someone or hope for the success of something:",
        answer: "here's to us",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 74,
        videoFile: video82,
        rusQuestion: "глоток",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to drink, taking only a very small amount at a time:",
        answer: "sip",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 73,
        videoFile: video80,
        rusQuestion: "покалывание",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "in a way that causes a feeling as if a lot of sharp points are being put quickly and lightly into your body:",
        answer: "tingling",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 72,
        videoFile: video79,
        rusQuestion: "сожалею об этом дне",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to feel very sorry about an event:",
        answer: "rue the day",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 71,
        videoFile: video78,
        rusQuestion: "поразить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to hit someone forcefully or to have a sudden powerful or damaging effect on someone",
        answer: "smite",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 70,
        videoFile: video78,
        rusQuestion: "отрывать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to tear or break something violently:",
        answer: "rend",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 69,
        videoFile: video77,
        rusQuestion: "тыква",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a large, round vegetable with hard, yellow or orange flesh:",
        answer: "pumpkin",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 68,
        videoFile: video73,
        rusQuestion: "почитаемый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to very much respect and admire someone or something:",
        answer: "revered",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 67,
        videoFile: video72,
        rusQuestion: "супружеский",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "connected with marriage:",
        answer: "marital",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 66,
        videoFile: video71,
        rusQuestion: "смягчитель",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a substance used to make something soft:",
        answer: "softener",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 65,
        videoFile: video71,
        rusQuestion: "поганка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a poisonous fungus with a round top and a narrow stem",
        answer: "toadstool",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 64,
        videoFile: video69,
        rusQuestion: "злой",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "morally wrong and bad:",
        answer: "wicked",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 63,
        videoFile: video67,
        rusQuestion: "вор-взломщик",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a person who illegally enters buildings and steals things",
        answer: "burglar",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 62,
        videoFile: video65,
        rusQuestion: "обувь",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "shoes, boots, or any other outer covering for the human foot:",
        answer: "footwear",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 61,
        videoFile: video64,
        rusQuestion: "похоть , страсть",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a very strong sexual desire:",
        answer: "lust",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 60,
        videoFile: video63,
        rusQuestion: "капля",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a small round-shaped amount of liquid:",
        answer: "drop",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 59,
        videoFile: video62,
        rusQuestion: "щепотка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a small amount of something, such as a powder, especially the amount that a person can hold between their first finger and thumb:",
        answer: "pinch",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 58,
        videoFile: video61,
        rusQuestion: "капризный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "When children are oooooo, or their behaviour is oooooo, they behave badly or do not do what they are told to do:",
        answer: "naughty",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 57,
        videoFile: video60,
        rusQuestion: "угнетенный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "governed in an unfair and cruel way and prevented from having opportunities and freedom:",
        answer: "oppressed",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 56,
        videoFile: video60,
        rusQuestion: "униженный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to cause people to feel that they or other people have no value and do not have the respect or good opinion of others:",
        answer: "degraded",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 55,
        videoFile: video58,
        rusQuestion: "зайти , заглянуть",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to visit briefly:",
        answer: "pop in",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 54,
        videoFile: video57,
        rusQuestion: "зелья",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a liquid that is believed to have a magical effect on someone who drinks it:",
        answer: "potion",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 53,
        videoFile: video57,
        rusQuestion: "заклинания",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an evil spell, bringing bad luck and trouble:",
        answer: "hex",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 52,
        videoFile: video56,
        rusQuestion: "изба",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a small house, usually in the countryside:",
        answer: "cottage",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 51,
        videoFile: video54,
        rusQuestion: "изысканный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "very beautiful and delicate: especially beautiful or admirable:",
        answer: "exquisite",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 50,
        videoFile: video54,
        rusQuestion: "блюдо",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "food prepared in a particular way as part of a meal:  a container, flatter than a bowl and sometimes with a lid, from which food can be served or which can be used for cooking:",
        answer: "dish",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 49,
        videoFile: video53,
        rusQuestion: "праздничный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "having or producing happy and enjoyable feelings suitable for a festival or other special occasion:",
        answer: "festive",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 48,
        videoFile: video52,
        rusQuestion: "расслабляться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to become more relaxed and less serious:",
        answer: "lighten up",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 47,
        videoFile: video51,
        rusQuestion: "пощажен",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "If something is ooooo, it is available to use because it is extra: to not hurt or destroy something or someone:",
        answer: "spared",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 46,
        videoFile: video50,
        rusQuestion: "обязан",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to be forced to do something or feel that you must do something:",
        answer: "obliged",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 45,
        videoFile: video50,
        rusQuestion: "сопровождать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to go with someone or to be provided or exist at the same time as something:  to go with someone or to exist at the same time as something:",
        answer: "accompany",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 44,
        videoFile: video49,
        rusQuestion: "неправильно судить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to form an opinion or idea about someone or something that is unfair or wrong:",
        answer: "misjudge",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 43,
        videoFile: video47,
        rusQuestion: "помет",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a group of animals that are born at the same time and have the same mother:   small pieces of rubbish that have been left lying on the ground in public places:",
        answer: "litter",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 42,
        videoFile: video46,
        rusQuestion: "умолять",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to ask someone to do or not do something in a very sincere, emotional, and determined way:",
        answer: "implore",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 41,
        videoFile: video45,
        rusQuestion: "кастрировать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to remove part of an animal's sexual organs, so that it cannot produce young animals:",
        answer: "neuter",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 40,
        videoFile: video44,
        rusQuestion: "орудие",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a gun: or weapon:",
        answer: "piece",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 39,
        videoFile: video43,
        rusQuestion: "мурлыкать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to make a quiet, continuous, soft sound:  (of a cat) to make a soft, low, continuous sound",
        answer: "purr",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 38,
        videoFile: video42,
        rusQuestion: "связь , узы",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to develop a close connection or strong relationship with someone, or to make someone do this:  to stick materials together, especially using glue, or to be stuck together like this:  a close connection joining two or more people:",
        answer: "bond",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 37,
        videoFile: video41,
        rusQuestion: "обидчивый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "angry and offended:",
        answer: "huffy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 36,
        videoFile: video40,
        rusQuestion: "зловещий",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "making you feel that something bad or evil might happen:  evil, or suggesting that something evil is going to happen:",
        answer: "sinister",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 35,
        videoFile: video39,
        rusQuestion: "подлый , презренный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "very unpleasant or bad, causing strong feelings of dislike:",
        answer: "despicable",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 34,
        videoFile: video38,
        rusQuestion: "пижамную вечеринку",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a party when a group of children spend the night at one child's house",
        answer: "slumber party",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 33,
        videoFile: video37,
        rusQuestion: "подсказать тебе",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to give someone information that is necessary or new:",
        answer: "clue you in",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 32,
        videoFile: video35,
        rusQuestion: "сонный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "being in a state between sleeping and being awake:",
        answer: "drowsy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 31,
        videoFile: video34,
        rusQuestion: "гладкий",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to make something perfectly flat or regular: having a surface or consisting of a substance that is perfectly regular and has no holes, lumps, or areas that rise or fall suddenly:",
        answer: "smooth",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 30,
        videoFile: video31,
        rusQuestion: "палочка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a special thin stick waved by a person who is performing magic tricks:",
        answer: "wand",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 29,
        videoFile: video29,
        rusQuestion: "лекарство",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a successful way of curing an illness or dealing with a problem or difficulty:",
        answer: "remedy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 28,
        videoFile: video28,
        rusQuestion: "животики",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the stomach, or the lower front part of the body:",
        answer: "tummies",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 27,
        videoFile: video27,
        rusQuestion: "очарованный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "affected by magic or seeming to be affected by magic:",
        answer: "enchanted",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
     {
        id: 26,
        videoFile: video26,
        rusQuestion: "чертовски",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "used instead of damn to express anger:",
        answer: "darn",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 25,
        videoFile: video24,
        rusQuestion: "незрелый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "not behaving in a way that is as calm and wise as people expect from someone of your age:",
        answer: "immature",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 24,
        videoFile: video21,
        rusQuestion: "напыщенный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "too serious and full of importance: feeling or showing that you think you are better or more important than other people:",
        answer: "pompous",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 23,
        videoFile: video18,
        rusQuestion: "бал",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a large, formal occasion where people dance",
        answer: "ball",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 22,
        videoFile: video16,
        rusQuestion: "подлый , мошеннически",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "used to describe people or behaviour that you disapprove of but still like:",
        answer: "rascally",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        videoFile: video15,
        rusQuestion: "приятное зрелище, больной , болячка , Взгляд усталых глаз",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a way of saying that you are very pleased to see someone or that you think someone is very attractive:",
        answer: "a sight for sore eyes",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        videoFile: video13,
        rusQuestion: "излечивать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to make someone with an illness healthy again:",
        answer: "cure",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        videoFile: video12,
        rusQuestion: "паутинка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the very thin thread that spiders produce to make webs",
        answer: "gossamer",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        videoFile: video11,
        rusQuestion: "страшное",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "causing fear or worry:",
        answer: "dreaded",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        videoFile: video10,
        rusQuestion: "конечность",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an arm or leg of a person or animal:",
        answer: "limb",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        videoFile: video9,
        rusQuestion: "палящий , обжигающий",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(of the weather) very hot:",
        answer: "scorching",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        videoFile: video8,
        rusQuestion: "очень горячий",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "extremely hot:",
        answer: "blistering",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        videoFile: video7,
        rusQuestion: "опасный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "extremely dangerous:",
        answer: "perilous",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        videoFile: video6,
        rusQuestion: "просить , искать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "past simple and past participle of seek (to try to find or get something, especially something that is not a physical object:)",
        answer: "sought",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        videoFile: video5,
        rusQuestion: "овладевать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to become strong; to be established:",
        answer: "take hold",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        videoFile: video4,
        rusQuestion: "по всему , повсюду",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "in every part, or during the whole period of time:",
        answer: "throughout",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    }
    
       
]


const vegas = [
   
    {
        id: 249,
        videoFile: video355,
        rusQuestion: "сосуществовать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to live or exist together at the same time or in the same place:",
        answer: "coexist",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 248,
        videoFile: video354,
        rusQuestion: "аромат , вкус",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the particular way a substance, esp. food or drink, is recognized from its taste and smell:",
        answer: "flavor",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 247,
        videoFile: video353,
        rusQuestion: "начинка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a substance, especially a sauce or pieces of food, that is put on top of other food to give extra flavour and to make it look attractive:",
        answer: "topping",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 246,
        videoFile: video352,
        rusQuestion: "пятна",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a dirty mark on something that is difficult to remove:",
        answer: "stains",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 245,
        videoFile: video351,
        rusQuestion: "отталкивать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the act of pushing someone or something unwanted away or of refusing him, her, or it",
        answer: "repulse",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 244,
        videoFile: video350,
        rusQuestion: "подчиненный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "having a lower or less important position:",
        answer: "subordinate",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 243,
        videoFile: video349,
        rusQuestion: "лучший пистолет",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the most important or powerful person in a particular sphere.",
        answer: "top gun",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 242,
        videoFile: video348,
        rusQuestion: "доступный всякому желающему",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "available and ready to be won or taken:",
        answer: "up for grabs",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 241,
        videoFile: video347,
        rusQuestion: "умственно отсталый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a word used to describe a person with a learning disability (= a condition that can have an effect on someone's ability to learn easily), which was used by doctors in the past but is now extremely offensive",
        answer: "retarded",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 240,
        videoFile: video346,
        rusQuestion: "фиолетовый бюстгальтер",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a piece of women's underwear that supports the breasts",
        answer: "purple bra",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 239,
        videoFile: video345,
        rusQuestion: "кружева",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a decorative cloth made by twisting thin thread in delicate patterns with holes in them:",
        answer: "lace",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 238,
        videoFile: video344,
        rusQuestion: "диван",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a sofa",
        answer: "couch",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 237,
        videoFile: video343,
        rusQuestion: "смириться , терпеть",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to be willing to accept someone or something that is unpleasant or not desirable:",
        answer: "put up with",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 236,
        videoFile: video342,
        rusQuestion: "кекс",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a small sweet cake that often has fruit inside it:",
        answer: "muffin",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 235,
        videoFile: video341,
        rusQuestion: "переусердствовать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to do something in a way that is too extreme:",
        answer: "overdo",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 234,
        videoFile: video340,
        rusQuestion: "крайне",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "extremely; very much:",
        answer: "sorely",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 233,
        videoFile: video339,
        rusQuestion: "намекая на это",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "suggesting ideas without saying them directly: ",
        answer: "insinuating",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 232,
        videoFile: video338,
        rusQuestion: "готов к этому",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "good enough for a particular activity:",
        answer: "up to it",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 231,
        videoFile: video337,
        rusQuestion: "мегера",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a female fox , an unpleasant woman",
        answer: "vixen",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 230,
        videoFile: video336,
        rusQuestion: "расколоть",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to (cause to) divide into two or more parts, especially along a particular line:",
        answer: "split",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 229,
        videoFile: video335,
        rusQuestion: "предоставить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to give or allow someone something, usually in an official way:",
        answer: "grant",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 228,
        videoFile: video334,
        rusQuestion: "десять центов",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an American or Canadian coin that has the value of ten cents",
        answer: "dime",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 227,
        videoFile: video333,
        rusQuestion: "судебные разбирательства",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the process of taking an argument between people or groups to a court of law:",
        answer: "litigation",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 226,
        videoFile: video332,
        rusQuestion: "консультирование",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the job or process of listening to someone and giving that person advice about his or her problems:",
        answer: "counseling",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 225,
        videoFile: video331,
        rusQuestion: "очаг",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a home, especially when seen as a place of comfort and love:",
        answer: "hearth",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 224,
        videoFile: video330,
        rusQuestion: "аварийная площадка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a place to sleep, especially for a single night or in an emergency.",
        answer: "crash pad",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 223,
        videoFile: video329,
        rusQuestion: "придурок",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an unpleasant person:",
        answer: "douche",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 222,
        videoFile: video328,
        rusQuestion: "клятвы",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to make a determined decision or promise to do something:",
        answer: "vows",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 221,
        videoFile: video328,
        rusQuestion: "старомодный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "not modern; belonging to or typical of a time in the past:",
        answer: "old-fashioned",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 220,
        videoFile: video327,
        rusQuestion: "да, есть дни",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "used to admit that something is true, before saying something else about it:",
        answer: "granted",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 219,
        videoFile: video326,
        rusQuestion: "приводящий в бешенство",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "extremely annoying:",
        answer: "infuriating",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 218,
        videoFile: video325,
        rusQuestion: "обязательство",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a promise or firm decision to do something:",
        answer: "commitment",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 217,
        videoFile: video324,
        rusQuestion: "святыня",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the quality of being holy:",
        answer: "sanctity",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 216,
        videoFile: video323,
        rusQuestion: "перепихнуться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to have sex:",
        answer: "get laid",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 215,
        videoFile: video322,
        rusQuestion: "обеспечить ее",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to give someone the things they need, such as money, food, or clothes:",
        answer: "provide for her",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 214,
        videoFile: video321,
        rusQuestion: "притворство , подделка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "something that is not what it seems to be and is intended to deceive people, or someone who pretends to be something they are not:",
        answer: "sham",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 213,
        videoFile: video320,
        rusQuestion: "сознательно , намеренно",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "while understanding the meaning of what you are doing:",
        answer: "knowingly",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 212,
        videoFile: video319,
        rusQuestion: "опьянение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the state of being drunk:",
        answer: "inebriation",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 211,
        videoFile: video318,
        rusQuestion: "увеличился в четыре раза",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to become four times as big, or to multiply a number or amount by four:",
        answer: "quadruple",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 210,
        videoFile: video317,
        rusQuestion: "четверть",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "in the US and Canada, a coin worth 25 cents",
        answer: "quarter",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 209,
        videoFile: video316,
        rusQuestion: "тошнота",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the feeling that you are going to vomit:",
        answer: "nausea",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 208,
        videoFile: video315,
        rusQuestion: "понятие",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a principle or idea:",
        answer: "concept",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 207,
        videoFile: video314,
        rusQuestion: "Еще бы",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "used to say ..yes.. very strongly, or to show that you are very sure about something:",
        answer: "you betcha",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 206,
        videoFile: video314,
        rusQuestion: "увернулся от пули",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "avoid (someone or something) by a sudden quick movement.",
        answer: "dodged",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 205,
        videoFile: video313,
        rusQuestion: "катастрофа предотвращена",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(an event that results in) great harm, damage, or death, or serious difficulty: to prevent something bad from happening:",
        answer: "disaster averted",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
     
]

